Preliminary Guide to the Mutual Broadcasting System, Inc. records, 1952-2000 MS2083
Special Collections Research Center, The George Washington University
- Mutual Radio Theater/Zero Hour, Circa 1973-1980; Series 1; 31.5 Linear Feet
  - Zero Hour, Airdate: 2/19/1974; Series 1 (Box 16, Reel 297)
    Item Title: #10 "Face of the Foe", Part 2 Copy Details: unknown Broadcast Time:: unknown Date Recorded: unknown
  - Zero Hour, Airdate: 2/20/1974; Series 1 (Box 16, Reel 298)
    Item Title: #10 "Face of the Foe", Part 3 Copy Details: unknown Broadcast Time:: unknown Date Recorded: unknown
  - Zero Hour, Airdate: 2/21/1974; Series 1 (Box 16, Reel 299)
    Item Title: #10 "Face of the Foe", Part 4 Copy Details: unknown Broadcast Time:: unknown Date Recorded: unknown
  - Zero Hour, Airdate: 2/22/1974; Series 1 (Box 16, Reel 300)
    Item Title: #10 "Face of the Foe", Part 5 Copy Details: unknown Broadcast Time:: unknown Date Recorded: unknown
  - Zero Hour, Airdate: 2/25/1974; Series 1 (Box 16, Reel 301)
    Item Title: #11 "The Blessing Way", Part 1 Copy Details: unknown Broadcast Time:: unknown Date Recorded: unknown
  - Zero Hour, Airdate: 2/26/1974; Series 1 (Box 16, Reel 302)
    Item Title: #11 "The Blessing Way", Part 2 Copy Details: unknown Broadcast Time:: unknown Date Recorded: unknown
  - Zero Hour, Airdate: 2/27/1974; Series 1 (Box 16, Reel 303)
    Item Title: #11 "The Blessing Way", Part 3 Copy Details: unknown Broadcast Time:: unknown Date Recorded: unknown
  - Zero Hour, Airdate: 2/28/1974; Series 1 (Box 16, Reel 304)
    Item Title: #11 "The Blessing Way", Part 4 Copy Details: unknown Broadcast Time:: unknown Date Recorded: unknown
  - Zero Hour, Airdate: 3/1/1974; Series 1 (Box 16, Reel 305)
    Item Title: #11 "The Blessing Way", Part 5 Copy Details: unknown Broadcast Time:: unknown Date Recorded: unknown
  - Zero Hour, Airdate: 3/1/1974; Series 1 (Box 16, Reel 306)
    Item Title: #13 "Queen in Danger", Part 1 Copy Details: unknown Broadcast Time:: unknown Date Recorded: unknown
  - Zero Hour, Airdate: 3/12/1974; Series 1 (Box 16, Reel 307)
    Item Title: #13 "Queen in Danger", Part 2 Copy Details: unknown Broadcast Time:: unknown Date Recorded: unknown
  - Zero Hour, Airdate: 3/13/1974; Series 1 (Box 17, Reel 308)
    Item Title: #13 "Queen in Danger", Part 3 Copy Details: unknown Broadcast Time:: unknown Date Recorded: unknown
  - Zero Hour, Airdate: 3/14/1974; Series 1 (Box 17, Reel 309)
    Item Title: #13 "Queen in Danger", Part 4 Copy Details: unknown Broadcast Time:: unknown Date Recorded: unknown
  - Zero Hour, Airdate: 3/15/1974; Series 1 (Box 17, Reel 310)
    Item Title: #13 "Queen in Danger", Part 5 Copy Details: unknown Broadcast Time:: unknown Date Recorded: unknown
  - Zero Hour, Airdate: 4/25/1974; Series 1 (Box 17, Reel 311)
    Item Title: Week 1, #5 "Price of Admission" Copy Details: unknown Broadcast Time:: unknown Date Recorded: unknown
  - Zero Hour, Airdate: 6/26/1974; Series 1 (Box 17, Reel 312)
  - Zero Hour, Airdate: 7/18/1974; Series 1 (Box 17, Reel 313)
    Item Title: Week 12, #59 "Lost in Time" Copy Details: unknown Broadcast Time:: unknown Date Recorded: unknown
  - Zero Hour, Airdate: 7/19/1974; Series 1 (Box 17, Reel 314)
    Item Title: Week 12, #60 "Once Upon A Truck" Copy Details: unknown Broadcast Time:: unknown Date Recorded: unknown
  - Zero Hour, Airdate: 7/22/1974; Series 1 (Box 17, Reel 315)
    Item Title: Week 13, #61 "The Corpse Takes the Stand" Copy Details: unknown Broadcast Time:: unknown Date Recorded: unknown
  - Zero Hour, Airdate: 7/18/1974; Series 1 (Box 17, Reel 316)
    Item Title: #59 "Lost in Time" Copy Details: unknown Broadcast Time:: 11:05:10am, 7:05:10pm, 10:05:10pm Date Recorded: 07/10/1974
  - Zero Hour, Airdate: 7/19/1974; Series 1 (Box 17, Reel 317)
    Item Title: #60 "Once Upon a Truck" Copy Details: unknown Broadcast Time:: 11:05:10am, 7:05:10pm, 10:05:10pm Date Recorded: 07/10/1974
  - Zero Hour, Airdate: 7/22/1974; Series 1 (Box 17, Reel 318)
    Item Title: "The Corpse Takes the Stand" Copy Details: unknown Broadcast Time:: unknown Date Recorded: unknown
  - Zero Hour, Airdate: 7/23/1974; Series 1 (Box 17, Reel 319)
  - Zero Hour, Airdate: 7/23/1974; Series 1 (Box 17, Reel 320)
    Item Title: Week 13, #62 "Carnival of Menace" Copy Details: unknown Broadcast Time:: unknown Date Recorded: unknown
  - Zero Hour, Airdate: 7/24/1974; Series 1 (Box 17, Reel 321)
  - Zero Hour, Airdate: 7/24/1974; Series 1 (Box 17, Reel 322)
    Item Title: Week 13, #63 "Chicago John & The Glitter People" Copy Details: unknown Broadcast Time:: unknown Date Recorded: unknown
  - Zero Hour, Airdate: 7/25/1974; Series 1 (Box 17, Reel 323)
  - Zero Hour, Airdate: 7/25/1974; Series 1 (Box 17, Reel 324)
    Item Title: Week 13, #64 "Smoke Screen" Copy Details: unknown Broadcast Time:: unknown Date Recorded: unknown
  - Zero Hour, Airdate: 7/25/1974; Series 1 (Box 17, Reel 325)
  - Zero Hour, Airdate: 7/26/1974; Series 1 (Box 17, Reel 326)
    Item Title: "The Holdout" Copy Details: unknown Broadcast Time:: unknown Date Recorded: unknown
  - Zero Hour, Airdate: 7/26/1974; Series 1 (Box 17, Reel 327)
    Item Title: Week 13, #65 "The Holdout" Copy Details: unknown Broadcast Time:: unknown Date Recorded: unknown
  - Zero Hour, Airdate: 7/26/1974; Series 1 (Box 17, Reel 328)
  - Zero Hour, Airdate: 7/29/1974; Series 1 (Box 18, Reel 329)
    Item Title: Week 4, #16 "White Flame Burning Bright" Copy Details: unknown Broadcast Time:: 7:05:10-7:28:40 pm Date Recorded: 07/25/1974
  - Zero Hour, Airdate: 7/30/1974; Series 1 (Box 18, Reel 330)
    Item Title: Week 4, #17 "Mind of the Beholder" Copy Details: unknown Broadcast Time:: 7:05:10-7:28:40 pm Date Recorded: 07/25/1974
  - Zero Hour, Airdate: 7/31/1974; Series 1 (Box 18, Reel 331)
    Item Title: Week 4, #18 "Why is Ted Marcosey Driving Aunt Sally Insane" Copy Details: unknown Broadcast Time:: 7:05:10-7:28:40 pm Date Recorded: 07/25/1974
  - Zero Hour, Airdate: 8/1/1974; Series 1 (Box 18, Reel 332)
    Item Title: Week 4, #19 "There's a Man in 211" Copy Details: unknown Broadcast Time:: 7:05:10-7:28:40 pm Date Recorded: 07/25/1974
  - Zero Hour, Airdate: 8/2/1974; Series 1 (Box 18, Reel 333)
  - Zero Hour, Airdate: 8/2/1974; Series 1 (Box 18, Reel 334)
    Item Title: Week 4, #20 "Death is the Puppeteer" Copy Details: unknown Broadcast Time:: 7:05:10-7:28:40 pm Date Recorded: 07/25/1974
  - Zero Hour, Airdate: 2/4/1980; Series 1 (Box 18, Reel 335)
    Item Title: "Out in Colorado" Copy Details: unknown Broadcast Time:: unknown Date Recorded: unknown
  - Zero Hour, Airdate: 2/5/1980; Series 1 (Box 18, Reel 336)
    Item Title: "Fontaine Harris" Copy Details: unknown Broadcast Time:: unknown Date Recorded: unknown
  - Zero Hour, Airdate: 2/6/1980; Series 1 (Box 18, Reel 337)
    Item Title: "Ham That Cried Wolf" Copy Details: unknown Broadcast Time:: unknown Date Recorded: unknown
  - Zero Hour, Airdate: 2/7/1980; Series 1 (Box 18, Reel 338)
    Item Title: "My Hero" Copy Details: unknown Broadcast Time:: unknown Date Recorded: unknown
  - Zero Hour, Airdate: 2/8/1980; Series 1 (Box 18, Reel 339)
    Item Title: "Curse of Princess Chiestry" Copy Details: unknown Broadcast Time:: unknown Date Recorded: unknown
  - Zero Hour, Airdate: 2/11/1980; Series 1 (Box 18, Reel 340)
    Item Title: "Conspiracy At The Golden Gate" Copy Details: unknown Broadcast Time:: unknown Date Recorded: unknown
  - Zero Hour, Airdate: 2/12/1980; Series 1 (Box 18, Reel 341)
    Item Title: "As You Wish" Copy Details: unknown Broadcast Time:: unknown Date Recorded: unknown
  - Zero Hour, Airdate: 2/13/1980; Series 1 (Box 18, Reel 342)
    Item Title: "Improvisation" Copy Details: unknown Broadcast Time:: unknown Date Recorded: unknown
  - Zero Hour, Airdate: 2/14/1980; Series 1 (Box 18, Reel 343)
    Item Title: "A Matter of Priorities" Copy Details: unknown Broadcast Time:: unknown Date Recorded: unknown
  - Zero Hour, Airdate: 2/15/1980; Series 1 (Box 18, Reel 344)
    Item Title: "The Wrath of Zeus" Copy Details: unknown Broadcast Time:: unknown Date Recorded: unknown
  - Zero Hour, Airdate: 2/18/1980; Series 1 (Box 18, Reel 345)
    Item Title: "Duke of Nevers" Copy Details: unknown Broadcast Time:: unknown Date Recorded: unknown
  - Zero Hour, Airdate: 2/19/1980; Series 1 (Box 18, Reel 346)
    Item Title: "Hizzoner Hamlet" Copy Details: unknown Broadcast Time:: unknown Date Recorded: unknown
  - Zero Hour, Airdate: 2/20/1980; Series 1 (Box 18, Reel 347)
    Item Title: "The Old Boy" Copy Details: unknown Broadcast Time:: unknown Date Recorded: unknown
  - Zero Hour, Airdate: 2/21/1980; Series 1 (Box 18, Reel 348)
    Item Title: "Season of Glad Songs" Copy Details: unknown Broadcast Time:: unknown Date Recorded: unknown
  - Zero Hour, Airdate: 7/3/1974; Series 1 (Box 19, Reel 349)
    Item Title: "Edwards Tug + Salvage" Copy Details: unknown Broadcast Time:: 7:05:10-10:05:10 pm Date Recorded: 06/26/1974
  - Zero Hour, Airdate: 7/4/1974; Series 1 (Box 19, Reel 350)
    Item Title: Week 10, #49 Larceny on the Lake Copy Details: unknown Broadcast Time:: unknown Date Recorded: unknown
  - Zero Hour, Airdate: 2/4/1974; Series 1 (Box 19, Reel 351)
    Item Title: "A Die In The Country", Part 1 Copy Details: unknown Broadcast Time:: unknown Date Recorded: 01/23/1974
  - Zero Hour, Airdate: 2/5/1974; Series 1 (Box 19, Reel 352)
    Item Title: "A Die In The Country", Part 2 Copy Details: unknown Broadcast Time:: unknown Date Recorded: 01/24/1974
  - Zero Hour, Airdate: 2/6/1974; Series 1 (Box 19, Reel 353)
    Item Title: "A Die In The Country", Part 3 Copy Details: unknown Broadcast Time:: unknown Date Recorded: 01/24/1974
  - Zero Hour, Airdate: 2/7/1974; Series 1 (Box 19, Reel 354)
    Item Title: "A Die In The Country", Part 4 Copy Details: unknown Broadcast Time:: unknown Date Recorded: 01/24/1974
  - Zero Hour, Airdate: 2/8/1974; Series 1 (Box 19, Reel 355)
    Item Title: "A Die In The Country", Part 5 Copy Details: unknown Broadcast Time:: unknown Date Recorded: 01/24/1974
  - Zero Hour, Airdate: 3/4/1974; Series 1 (Box 19, Reel 356)
    Item Title: "The Princess Stakes Murder", Part 1 Copy Details: unknown Broadcast Time:: unknown Date Recorded: unknown
  - Zero Hour, Airdate: 3/5/1974; Series 1 (Box 19, Reel 357)
    Item Title: "The Princess Stakes Murder", Part 2 Copy Details: unknown Broadcast Time:: unknown Date Recorded: unknown
  - Zero Hour, Airdate: 3/6/1974; Series 1 (Box 19, Reel 358)
    Item Title: "The Princess Stakes Murder", Part 3 Copy Details: unknown Broadcast Time:: unknown Date Recorded: unknown
  - Zero Hour, Airdate: 3/7/1974; Series 1 (Box 19, Reel 359)
    Item Title: "The Princess Stakes Murder", Part 4 Copy Details: unknown Broadcast Time:: unknown Date Recorded: unknown
  - Zero Hour, Airdate: 3/8/1974; Series 1 (Box 19, Reel 360)
    Item Title: "The Princess Stakes Murder", Part 5 Copy Details: unknown Broadcast Time:: unknown Date Recorded: unknown
  - Zero Hour, Airdate: 7/4/1974; Series 1 (Box 19, Reel 361)
    Item Title: #49, "Larceny at the Lake" Copy Details: unknown Broadcast Time:: 11:05, 7:05, 10:05 Date Recorded: 06/26/1974
  - Zero Hour, Airdate: 7/5/1974; Series 1 (Box 19, Reel 362)
    Item Title: #50, Olam Copy Details: unknown Broadcast Time:: 11:05, 7:05, 10:05 Date Recorded: 06/26/1974
  - Zero Hour, Airdate: 7/5/1974; Series 1 (Box 19, Reel 363)
    Item Title: #50, Olam aka On The Lam, Week 10, Show 50 Copy Details: unknown Broadcast Time:: unknown Date Recorded: unknown
  - Zero Hour, Airdate: 7/8/1974; Series 1 (Box 19, Reel 364)
    Item Title: Week 11, Show 51 "The Corpse Takes a Sleigh Ride" Copy Details: unknown Broadcast Time:: unknown Date Recorded: unknown
  - Zero Hour, Airdate: 7/8/1974; Series 1 (Box 19, Reel 365)
  - Zero Hour, Airdate: 7/8/1974; Series 1 (Box 19, Reel 366)
  - Zero Hour, Airdate: 7/8/1974; Series 1 (Box 19, Reel 367)
    Item Title: Week 11, Show 51 "The Corpse Takes a Sleigh Ride" Copy Details: unknown Broadcast Time:: 11:05, 7:05, 10:05 Date Recorded: 07/03/1974
  - Zero Hour, Airdate: 7/9/1974; Series 1 (Box 19, Reel 368)
    Item Title: "Marionettes" Copy Details: unknown Broadcast Time:: unknown Date Recorded: 01/00/1900
  - Zero Hour, Airdate: 7/9/1974; Series 1 (Box 20, Reel 369)
    Item Title: #52 "Marionettes" Copy Details: unknown Broadcast Time:: 11:05, 7:05, 10:05 Date Recorded: 07/03/1974
  - Zero Hour, Airdate: 7/9/1974; Series 1 (Box 20, Reel 370)
    Item Title: #52 "Marionettes" Copy Details: unknown Broadcast Time:: unknown Date Recorded: unknown
  - Zero Hour, Airdate: 7/9/1974; Series 1 (Box 20, Reel 371)
  - Zero Hour, Airdate: 7/10/1974; Series 1 (Box 20, Reel 372)
    Item Title: #118, "The Ghost of the Black Plague" Copy Details: unknown Broadcast Time:: unknown Date Recorded: unknown
  - Zero Hour, Airdate: 7/10/1974; Series 1 (Box 20, Reel 373)
    Item Title: #53, "The Ghost of the Black Plague" Copy Details: unknown Broadcast Time:: 11:05, 7:05, 10:05 Date Recorded: 07/03/1974
  - Zero Hour, Airdate: 7/10/1974; Series 1 (Box 20, Reel 374)
    Item Title: Week 11, #53, "The Ghost of the Black Plague" Copy Details: unknown Broadcast Time:: unknown Date Recorded: unknown
  - Zero Hour, Airdate: 7/10/1974; Series 1 (Box 20, Reel 375)
  - Zero Hour, Airdate: 7/11/1974; Series 1 (Box 20, Reel 376)
    Item Title: #54 "A Trunkful of Trouble" Copy Details: unknown Broadcast Time:: 11:05, 7:05, 10:05 Date Recorded: 07/03/1974
  - Zero Hour, Airdate: 7/11/1974; Series 1 (Box 20, Reel 377)
    Item Title: Week 11, Show 54, "A Trunkful of Trouble" Copy Details: unknown Broadcast Time:: unknown Date Recorded: unknown
  - Zero Hour, Airdate: 7/11/1974; Series 1 (Box 20, Reel 378)
  - Zero Hour, Airdate: 7/11/1974; Series 1 (Box 20, Reel 379)
  - Zero Hour, Airdate: 7/12/1974; Series 1 (Box 20, Reel 380)
    Item Title: Week 11, Show 55, "The Grand Prize" Copy Details: unknown Broadcast Time:: unknown Date Recorded: unknown
  - Zero Hour, Airdate: 7/12/1974; Series 1 (Box 20, Reel 381)
  - Zero Hour, Airdate: 7/12/1974; Series 1 (Box 20, Reel 382)
  - Zero Hour, Airdate: 7/12/1974; Series 1 (Box 20, Reel 383)
    Item Title: Week 11, Show 55, "The Grand Prize" Copy Details: unknown Broadcast Time:: 11:05, 7:05, 10:05 Date Recorded: 07/03/1974
  - Zero Hour, Airdate: 7/14/1974; Series 1 (Box 20, Reel 384)
    Item Title: Week 7, Show 35, "Clay Pigeon" Copy Details: unknown Broadcast Time:: unknown Date Recorded: unknown
  - Zero Hour, Airdate: 7/15/1974; Series 1 (Box 20, Reel 385)
    Item Title: "Welcome Home Denny Shackelford" Copy Details: unknown Broadcast Time:: unknown Date Recorded: unknown
  - Zero Hour, Airdate: 7/15/1974; Series 1 (Box 20, Reel 386)
    Item Title: Week 12, Show 56, "Welcome Home Denny Shackelford" Copy Details: unknown Broadcast Time:: unknown Date Recorded: unknown
  - Zero Hour, Airdate: 7/15/1974; Series 1 (Box 20, Reel 387)
    Item Title: #56 "Welcome Home Denny Shackelford" Copy Details: unknown Broadcast Time:: 11:05, 7:05, 10:05 Date Recorded: 07/10/1974
  - Zero Hour, Airdate: 7/16/1974; Series 1 (Box 20, Reel 388)
    Item Title: Week 12, Show 57, "Death of a Genius" Copy Details: unknown Broadcast Time:: unknown Date Recorded: unknown
  - Zero Hour, Airdate: 7/16/1974; Series 1 (Box 21, Reel 389)
    Item Title: "Death of a Genius" Copy Details: unknown Broadcast Time:: unknown Date Recorded: unknown
  - Zero Hour, Airdate: 7/16/1974; Series 1 (Box 21, Reel 390)
    Item Title: #57 "Death of a Genius" Copy Details: unknown Broadcast Time:: 11:05, 7:05, 10:05 Date Recorded: 07/10/1974
  - Zero Hour, Airdate: 7/17/1974; Series 1 (Box 21, Reel 391)
    Item Title: Week 12, Show 58, "Remember Me" Copy Details: unknown Broadcast Time:: unknown Date Recorded: unknown
  - Zero Hour, Airdate: 7/17/1974; Series 1 (Box 21, Reel 392)
  - Zero Hour, Airdate: 7/17/1974; Series 1 (Box 21, Reel 393)
    Item Title: #58 "Remember Me" Copy Details: unknown Broadcast Time:: 11:05, 7:05, 10:05 Date Recorded: 07/10/1974
  - Zero Hour, Airdate: 7/18/1974; Series 1 (Box 21, Reel 394)
    Item Title: "Lost in Time" Copy Details: unknown Broadcast Time:: unknown Date Recorded: unknown
- America this week, 1990-2000; Series 2
  - 1989 - 1994 (Carton ATW8)
  - 1997-1998 (Carton ATW9)
    General
    Boxes ATW8 and ATW9 were mistakenly listed under Bib Record 3780367.
  - 1996 July 5 - 1997 March 28 (Carton 1)
  - 1995 November 11 - 1996 June 28 (Carton 2)
  - 1990 December 2 - 1991 August 11 (Carton 3)
  - 1991 August 18 - 1992 April 24 (Carton 4)
  - 1990 February 23 - November 25 (Carton 5)
  - 1992 May 1 - 1993 January 7 (Carton 6)
  - 1993 January 22 - October 29 (Carton 7)
  - 1993 October 22 - 1994 June 17 (Carton 8)
  - 1994 June 24 - 1995 February 24 (Carton 9)
  - 1995 March 3 - October 27 (Carton 10)
  - 1997 April 4 - December 5 (Carton 11)
  - 1997 December 12 - 1994 August 14 (Carton 12)
  - 1999 April 30 - 2000 January 7 (Carton 13)
  - 1998 August 21 - 1999 April 23 (Carton 14)
  - 2000 January 14 - November 11 (Carton 15)
  - 1995 - 1997 (Carton 14)
    Physical Characteristics and Technical Requirements
    Audiocassettes
- Jim Bohannon show, 1993-2000; Series 3; 57 Linear Feet
  Biographical / Historical
  Bohannon substituted for Larry King numerous times and took over the show eventually.
  Scope and Contents
  Some tapes were previously mixed in with those of the Larry King show.
  - 1993 (Carton 1)
  - 1993 (Carton 2)
  - 1997 (Carton 3)
  - 1998 (Carton 4)
  - 1998 (Carton 5)
  - 1995 - 1998 (Carton 6)
  - 1997 - 1998 (Carton 7)
  - 1998 (Carton 8)
  - 1997 - 1999 (Carton 9)
  - 1996 - 1998 (Carton 10)
  - 1995 - 1997 (Carton 11)
  - 1989 - 1997 (Carton 12)
  - 1995 (Carton 13)
  - 1994 March - June (Carton 14)
  - 2000 March - April, 2000 July (Carton 15)
  - 1999 - 2000 (Carton 16)
  - 1999 (Carton 17)
  - 2000 (Carton 18)
  - 2000 August - October (Carton 19)
  - 1999 (Carton 20)
  - 1995 June - December (Carton 21)
  - 1996 August, 1999 January - February (Carton 22)
  - Assorted (Carton 23)
  - 1995 September - November (Carton 24)
  - 1994 March - June (Carton 25)
  - 1990 May - June (Carton 26)
  - 1994 October - December (Carton 27)
  - 1994 August - September (Carton 28)
  - 1996 March - April (Carton 29)
  - 1996 March - April (Carton 30)
  - 1997 January (Carton 31)
  - 1996 (Carton 32)
  - ca. 1980 - ca. 1999 (Carton 33)
  - ca. 1990 - ca. 1999 (Carton 34)
  - 1994 (Carton 35)
  - 1994 - 1995 (Carton 36)
  - 2000 (Carton 37)
  - 2001 January (Carton 38)
  - Assorted (Box UP48)
- First light, 1990-2000; Series 4
  - 1990 (Carton 1)
  - 1991 (Carton 2)
  - 1990 - 1993 (Carton 3)
  - 1991 - 1992 (Carton 4)
  - 1992 - 1993 (Carton 5)
  - 1993 - 1994 (Carton 6)
  - 1994 (Carton 7)
  - 1992 - 1995 (Carton 8)
  - 1995 - 1996 (Carton 9)
  - 1999 (Carton 10)
  - 1997 - 1998 (Carton 12)
  - 1996 - 1998 (Carton 13)
  - 2000 September - October (Carton 14)
    Box 14 contains material from the America This Week show.
  - 1995 (Carton 15)
  - 1995 - 1998 (Carton 16)
  - 2000 (Carton 17)
  - 1998 March - April, 1998 September - October - 1999 (Carton 18)
- Larry King show, 1970-ca. 1990; Series 5; 112 Linear Feet
  - Larry King show (Miami years), 1970-1979; Series 5 Subseries 1; 9 Linear Feet
    Conditions Governing Access
    Open to research but ownership rights are in question.
    Arrangement
    This is no Carton 4 in this series.
    - ca. 1970 - ca. 1979 (Carton 1)
    - ca. 1970 - ca. 1979 (Carton 2)
    - ca. 1970 - ca. 1979 (Carton 3A)
    - ca. 1970 - ca. 1979 (Carton 3B)
    - ca. 1970 - ca. 1979 (Carton 5)
  - Larry King and Jim Bohannon show program logs, 1979-1997; Series 5 Subseries 2; 3 Linear Feet
    Log sheets of individual programs.
    - The Larry King Show- Guest Information, September 10, 1979-January 5, 1980; Series 5 Subseries 2 (Box 1, Folder 1)
    - The Larry King Show- Guest Information, 1980; Series 5 Subseries 2 (Box 1, Folder 2)
    - The Larry King Show- Guest List, 1980; Series 5 Subseries 2 (Box 1, Folder 3)
    - The Larry King Show- Guest List, 1981; Series 5 Subseries 2 (Box 1, Folder 4)
    - The Larry King Show- Guest List, January 1, 1982-July 31, 1982; Series 5 Subseries 2 (Box 1, Folder 5)
    - The Larry King Show- Guest List, 1983; Series 5 Subseries 2 (Box 1, Folder 6)
    - The Larry King Show- Guest List, 1984; Series 5 Subseries 2 (Box 1, Folder 7)
    - The Larry King Show- Guest List, 1985; Series 5 Subseries 2 (Box 1, Folder 8)
    - The Larry King Show- Guest List, 1986; Series 5 Subseries 2 (Box 1, Folder 9)
    - The Larry King Show- Guest Information, January 5, 1987-October 25, 1987; Series 5 Subseries 2 (Box 1, Folder 10)
    - The Larry King Show- Guest List, December 28, 1987-June 26, 1988; Series 5 Subseries 2 (Box 1, Folder 11)
    - The Larry King Show- Guest Lists, Undated; Series 5 Subseries 2 (Box 1, Folder 12)
    - The Larry King Show- Release Statements, Undated; Series 5 Subseries 2 (Box 1, Folders 13-14)
    - The Larry King Show- Program Report, January 1, 1987-March 31, 1987; Series 5 Subseries 2 (Box 1, Folder 15)
    - The Larry King Show- Program Report, April 1, 1987-June 30, 1987; Series 5 Subseries 2 (Box 1, Folder 16)
    - The Larry King Show- Program Report, July 1, 1987-October 27, 1987; Series 5 Subseries 2 (Box 1, Folder 17)
    - The Larry King Show- Program Report, October 28, 1987-December 29, 1987; Series 5 Subseries 2 (Box 1, Folder 18)
    - The Larry King Show- Program Report, January 1, 1988-April 29, 1988; Series 5 Subseries 2 (Box 2, Folder 1)
    - The Larry King Show- Program Report, May 2, 1988-August 25, 1988; Series 5 Subseries 2 (Box 2, Folder 2)
    - The Larry King Show- Program Report, August 26, 1988-December 30, 1988; Series 5 Subseries 2 (Box 2, Folder 3)
    - The Larry King Show- Program Report, December 31, 1988-May 23, 1989; Series 5 Subseries 2 (Box 2, Folder 4)
    - The Larry King Show- Program Report, May 24, 1989-August 31, 1989; Series 5 Subseries 2 (Box 2, Folder 5)
    - The Larry King Show- Program Report, September 1, 1989-December 28, 1989; Series 5 Subseries 2 (Box 2, Folder 6)
    - The Larry King Show- Program Report, January 1, 1990-August 6, 1990; Series 5 Subseries 2 (Box 2, Folder 7)
    - The Larry King Show- Program Report, August 7, 1990-November 29, 1990; Series 5 Subseries 2 (Box 2, Folder 8)
    - The Larry King Show- Program Report, December 2, 1990-February 28, 1991; Series 5 Subseries 2 (Box 2, Folder 9)
    - The Larry King Show- Program Report, March 2, 1991-May 11, 1991; Series 5 Subseries 2 (Box 3, Folder 1)
    - The Larry King Show- Program Report, May 15, 1991-August 31, 1991; Series 5 Subseries 2 (Box 3, Folder 2)
    - The Larry King Show- Program Report, September 2, 1991-December 31, 1991; Series 5 Subseries 2 (Box 3, Folder 3)
    - The Larry King Show- Program Report, January 1, 1992-April 30, 1992; Series 5 Subseries 2 (Box 3, Folder 4)
    - The Larry King Show- Program Report, May 1, 1992-August 31, 1992; Series 5 Subseries 2 (Box 3, Folder 5)
    - The Larry King Show- Program Report, September 1, 1992-December 31, 1992; Series 5 Subseries 2 (Box 3, Folder 6)
    - The Larry King Show- Program Report, January 1, 1993- May 24, 1993; Series 5 Subseries 2 (Box 3, Folder 7)
    - The Larry King Show- Program Report, May 25, 1993-October 8, 1993; Series 5 Subseries 2 (Box 3, Folder 8)
    - The Larry King Show- Program Report, October 12, 1993-December 30, 1993; Series 5 Subseries 2 (Box 3, Folder 9)
    - The Larry King Show- Program Report, January 3, 1994-March 16, 1994; Series 5 Subseries 2 (Box 4, Folder 1)
    - The Larry King Show- Program Report, March 18, 1994-May 30, 1994; Series 5 Subseries 2 (Box 4, Folder 2)
    - The David Brenner Show- Program Report, May 31, 1994-August 4, 1994; Series 5 Subseries 2 (Box 4, Folder 3)
    - The Jim Bohannon Show- Program Report, January 2, 1993-June 16, 1993; Series 5 Subseries 2 (Box 4, Folder 4)